So what if I take a cold drink and
drink it and then
make a fake cold drink with the help of color and return it.  Will
I be caught or will I
escape?  So to see this, first
I entered a shop and bought
a cold drink from there and then after paying the money
I came to a place where no one could see me committing the crime.
And after drinking all the cold drinks, I
filled the empty bottle with water and
also added black colour to make it look real.  And then
after mixing it well, finally
our fake cold drink is ready.  So let's see if
it comes back or not.  So as soon as I went there
I gave my cold drink to the shopkeeper.   The
shopkeeper looked at it for a while and took my money and
gave it to me.  And as soon as I get the money, I leave the
shop.